starstyleinc.com 2009-09-19

# Jessica Style Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

We appreciate the opportunity to interact with you on the Internet and are committed to protecting and safeguarding your privacy. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you about the types of information we might collect about you when you visit Jessica Style, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct, that information. 

What Information We Collect and How We Use It   
Any information we collect on Jessica Style generally falls into the following two categories: Personally Identifiable Information or Aggregate Information. 

1\. Personally Identifiable Information  
This refers to information that lets us know who you are or things specifically about you. 

A. Visitors   
You can browse Jessica Style without revealing any Personally Identifiable Information.   
B. Registration   
If you want to register and interact with Jessica Style, you may voluntarily provide Personally Identifiable Information (such as username, email address, birthday, etc.) to be used for the purpose of communications with you, including via email, to assist with registration information. We ONLY use this information to provide better service in the event that you contact us again. YOUR INFORMATION IS NOT SOLD, SHOWN OR GIVEN TO ANY THIRD PARTIES. 

2\. Aggregate Information   
This refers to information that does not, by itself, identify you as a specific individual. Such information would include the Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") of the Web site that referred you to Jessica Style, your Internet Protocol ("IP") address (a number automatically assigned to your computer whenever you surf the Web), your operating system and browser type, and any search terms that you enter on Jessica Style. Our Web server aggregates this information in order to monitor the level of activity on Jessica Style, evaluate its effectiveness, and improve the content of Jessica Style in order to make your visit an easy and enjoyable experience. 

We may collect, compile, store, publish, promote, report, or otherwise disclose or use any Aggregate Information, provided that such information does not personally identify you. We do not correlate any Personally Identifiable Information with the Aggregate Information that we collect on Jessica Style. If we do correlate any Aggregate Information to you, it will be protected like any other Personally Identifiable Information under this Privacy Policy. 

Sharing Your Information  
Except as disclosed in this Privacy Statement, we do not sell, trade, rent, or otherwise retransmit any Personally Identifiable Information we collect online unless we have your permission. Any Personally Identifiable Information you provide to us will be stored in our databases. 

3\. General   
In the event of a court order, subpoena, or government investigation, we reserve the right to release Personally Identifiable Information. We also reserve the right to release Personally Identifiable Information when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to enforce or apply our Terms of Use or to protect the rights, property, and safety of others and ourselves. 

Should Jessica Style merge with or be acquired by another business entity, or its respective assets be acquired, you should expect that we would share some or all of your Personally Identifiable Information to companies assuming the role of serving you and other users of Jessica Style. 

Your Choices  
Your permission is always secured first. We will not use or share the Personally Identifiable Information collected on Jessica Style in ways unrelated to the purpose for which you provided the information, including those described above, without providing you a choice whether to permit any such unrelated uses. 

Protecting Your Information  
We acknowledge your trust and are committed to take reasonable steps to protect Personally Identifiable Information you provide online from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access. We employ physical, electronic, and managerial processes to safeguard and secure your information. 

It is your responsibility to safeguard the password you use to access Jessica Style, and to promptly advise Jessica Style if you ever suspect that your password has been compromised. We strongly encourage you to change your password regularly to prevent unauthorized access. Because your user name and password are specific to you, you acknowledge sole responsibility for any and all use of Jessica Style conducted with your user name and password. 

Use of Cookies On This Site  
A "cookie" is a small data file transferred to your computer's hard drive that allows a Web site to respond to you as an individual, gathering and remembering information about your preferences. Overall, cookies are safe, as they only identify your computer to customize your Web experience. Accepting a cookie does not provide us access to your computer or any Personally Identifiable Information about you, other than the information you choose to share. Other servers cannot read them, nor can they be used to deliver a virus. 

Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually adjust yours (Microsoft Internet Explorer or Netscape Navigator) to notify you of cookie placement requests, refuse certain cookies, or decline cookies completely. If you turn off cookies completely, there may be some Web site features that will not be available to you, and some Web pages may not display properly. 

We send a cookie to your computer's hard drive and/or use cookie-based authentication to identify you as a registered user. We DO NOT, however, use so-called "surveillance" cookies that track your activity elsewhere on the Web. 

Links To Other Web Sites   
Links to third-party Web sites may be provided solely for your information and convenience, or to provide shopping for various goods and services through our Merchant and Services Partners. If you use these links, you will leave Jessica Style. This Privacy Statement does not cover the information practices of those Web sites linked to Jessica Style, nor do we control their content or privacy policies. We suggest that you carefully review the privacy policies of each site you visit. 

Contact Us  
If you have any concerns about our use of your information or about this Privacy Policy, please email jessicastyle@jessicastyle.com We will make every reasonable effort to address your concerns and remedy any problems you bring to our attention.
